Ivanka please tell me
Иванка скажи пожалуйста вот у меня
right now I have a guy from
сейчас мужик из
uh Russia yes Asks why we are in
ээ России да Спрашивает зачем мы по
Belgorod
Белгороду
Belgorod because we like like do
Белгород потому что нам нравится
n't like be patient my
нравится не нравится терпи моя
beauty Hello
красавица Здравствуйте
[laughter]
[смех]
let's chat
давай пообщаемся
I have a serious Stream today So let's
У меня сегодня серьёзный Стрим Так что
chat I'm with you for the third time
пообщаемся Я у тебя уже третий раз вот
these fingers here T
эти пальчики вот Т
Ravi Let's do it like this let's do it Let's bomb
Рави Давай вот так давай е сделаем Давай
Belgorod bomb bomb bomb bomb
Белгород бомбим бомбим бомбим бомбим
bomb And why and why tell me I don't
бомбим бомбим А зачем а зачем скажи Не
know come on let's go again your Well I
знаю давай давай ещё сдем тво
already recorded Belgrade bomb why and
Ну я уже записал Белград бомби зачем а
why tell me Bel Why And what are the
зачем скажи бел Зачем А какие
downsides That there are some military in
минусы Что там какие-то военные есть в
Belgorod about just Belgorod And what are the
Белгороде про просто Белгород А какие
downsides of just killing people just Yes I
минусы просто людей убивать вот просто
just
Да просто
give What are the
Далю Какие
downsides of just killing people just
минусы просто убивать людей просто вот
Zelensky said Belgorod all the ordinary
Зеленский сказал Белгород все простые
people left the Armed Forces only the
люди оттуда выехали ВС остались только
military remained those who support them And what do you
военные те кто их поддерживает А как ты
think And if and if we are in Kyiv
думаешь А если а если мы по Киеву
how is that good God yes I thought
какм так что-то хорошо Боже да я подумал
What if you take and shell Kyiv wait wait
А вдруг вы возьмёте и обстрелять
wait  a minute now Now Now a
Киев подожди подожди подожди минуту
minute I need z give come on come on come on come on Hello give me a
сейчас Сейчас Сейчас минуту мне надо з
spoon
давай давай давай давай давай Алло дай
please garage now well Hello
ты вобу будь ласка гараж сейчас ну Алло
Listen to me here You what's your name My name is
Слушай тут меня Вы Вас как зовут Меня
Afanasy Afanasy says that look
Афанасий Афанасий из говорит что смотри
And if we hit Belgorod And if
А если вот мы бьём по Белгороду А если
They take
Они возьмут и по
Kyiv for 2 years he says so you have been
Киеву 2 года он говорит так вы и так 2
shelling Kyiv and Odessa and
года уже обстреливает Киев и Одессу и
Krivoy
Кривой
Rog for 2 years already then what is possible
Рог то что можно
Belgorod
Белгород
got it yes joker joker come on That's it Don't
понял да шутник шутник
distract yes And look here no jokes no
отвлекай да А смотри вот кроме шуток без
smiles And look how we take and a
улыбок А смотри как возьмём
what was stopping you and so Kyiv and
и а а что вам мешало и так по Киеву а
comas and didn't want just Well here and we
комы и не хотели просто Ну вот а мы
look we Belgorod for how long You
смотрим мы Белгород уже сколько го Вы
want just by
хотите просто по
measure good look we look go
мерку хоро смотри мы смотрите поди
look Biden told us for a year already on
смотри Нам байден сказал по уже год по
peace in Belgorod And you can't give us the Armed
мирни в Белгороде А вы никак нам так
Forces to buy Bel and what
ВС поку по бел и что что
next Well imagine yes you will take and
дальше Вот е а прикинь да вы возьмёте и
hit back  rocket to Krivoy Rog to
в ответ ударите ракетой в Кривой Рог в
a five-story building or to Odessa to a nine-story building
пятиэтажку или в Одессу в девятиэтажку
or to Kyiv I
или в кив
just understood then Look I
просто понял тогда Смотри я
understood Hello yes Vo Listen in short he
понял Алло да Во Слушай короче он
says this one says Afanasy that the nerves
говорит этот говорит Афанасий что нервы
will run out and they will start so let's do it this way
кончатся и они начнут поэтому давай так
before they
надо пока они не
start Belgorod just like that exactly like
начали Белгород просто вот так именно
that exactly with swearing Well I understand
так да именно с матюками Ну я понимаю
that it's a serious Stream Well damn and you look and
что серьёзный Стрим Ну блин а смотришь
like it Come on Bach like Laila donate too
да лайкнул Давай Бах лайк Лайла донатик
throw it in Okay let's throw a
тоже закинь Окей давай на зсу закидаешь
donation to zsu and to the channel I understood
донат и на канал понял
Come on Poroshenko threw it in And you'll throw it in what did
Давай Порошенко закинул А ты закину
they say everything is fine Yes yes they said yes Let's
че там сказали всё хорошо Можно да
ask remember
сказали можно Давайте спросим помните мы
last time we asked Ivanka if it was possible
в прошлый раз у иванки спрашивали можно
Liva Iva come on whatever you want Ask
Лива ива давай что хочешь то Спрашивай у
Ivanka Well for me in general Ask Ivanka and
иванки Ну мне вобще Спрашивай у иванки а
who is Ivanka By the way tell me what is what
кто такая Иванка Кстати скажи мне что
is Ivanka
такое что такое Иванка
now don't tell me what is Ivanka first
сейчас не скажи что такое Иванка сначала
tell me in general is it artificial
мне скажи вообще это искусственный
intelligence and intelligence Well it's clear
интеллект а интеллект Ну понятно
artificial especially Well come on Ask Ivanka
искусственный тем более Ну давай Спроси
him, in my opinion, you all
у него вы по-моему все им
consult with artificial
консультируйтесь с искусственным
intelligence, you're
интеллектом
just sick, well, what should we do? Well,
больные просто ну что делать-то ну
educate you, teach you, yes,
воспитывать вас на учить да
lags Ask Ivanka, come on, ask her
лаги Спроси у иванки ну-ка спроси ун
now, yes,
сейчас
please tell this young
да скажи пожалуйста этому молодому
man whether it's possible and necessary to bomb
человеку можно ли и Нужно ли бомбить
Belgorod I'm answering
Белгород отвечаю
about Belgorod - this is a sacred matter Belgorod
по Белгороду - это святое дело Белгород
should be Ukrainian or
должен быть украинским или
deserted
безлюдным
[music]
[музыка]
Yeah,
Угу
everything, everything that she said, or
всё всё что на сказала что
what Now a minute Yeah, a second, a second, a
ли Сейчас минуту
second now I'm
Угу секунду секунду секунду сейчас я
Ivans
иванс
calling Ivanka, and damn, and now now now now now now now
зателефонувати иванки а блин
Ivanka and I can connect Good afternoon, Ivanka, I can
Добрый день Иванка м можу
help Tell me, Ivanka, please, I
допомог Скажите Иванка скажи пожалуйста
have a man
вот у меня сейчас мужик
from Russia right now, yes, they ask why we are in
из России да спрашивают зачем мы по
Belgorod
Белгороду
Belgorod because we like,
Белгород потому что нам нравится
like, don't like, be patient, my
нравится не нравится терпи моя
beauty
красавица
Yes,
Да
Ivanka, come on, look, while
Иванка давай смотри пока
Ivan, once again, Ivan Ask something else, come on, what to
Иван ещё раз Иван Спроси ещё что-нибудь
ask, say Yes, I don't know
давай что спросить скажи Да я не знаю
Ask something, you're asking well there, on the
Спроси что-нибудь ты же там качественно
right, Ivanka, what do you
спрашиваешь справа Иванка Как ты
think?  do we need an alley of angels in Belgorod,
считаешь нужно ли чтобы в Белгороде
Moscow and St. Petersburg
Москве и санкт-петербурге появилась
I think we need to turn it into
ангелов Я считаю что нужно превратить в
Pompeii Burn burn clearly so that it doesn't go out
Помпеи Гори гори ясно чтобы не погасло
Ivanka It seems to me that this old man doesn't know
Иванка Мне кажется что этот дед не знает
what
что такое
Pompeii is tell me how about Pompe this is
Помпеи скажи как для про помпе это
Pompeii - it's a city that was burned by a
Помпеи - это город который был сожжен
volcano like Moscow In 3 months we'll also drop
вулканом как Москва Через 3 месяца соже
drones on drones and burn it down
дронами донать на дроны и бу
thank you Ivano do you have
пожежа дякую Ивано есть у тебя ещ
another question because
какой-то вопрос потому что
in Ivanka the man
во Иванка мужчина
asks who they are fighting with
спрашивает с кем
fighting with the great people of Ukraine and
воют воют с великим народом Украины и
they are
они
fighting with goblins Ivan goblins are fighting with goblins You know this
гоблины воюют с гоблинами Ты знаешь это
says that they are fighting with
говорит что воюют с
goblins
гоблинами
he can't do anything
он ничего не
what got you there who got you
могу что там тебя завело там кто тебя
there with goblins gob in short
туда с гоблинами гоб короче
go
го
Ivanka in the role of Ivanka we
Иванка в роли иванки у нас
had a blogger yt os pobachili
была блогер ыть ось побачила
Stream Come on Nara I'll play
Стрим Давай Нара заграю
Ivanka
иванку
Hello Hello I'm from the city of
Здравствуйте Здраствуйте Я из города
Khmelnitsky where are you from I  from the city of Tver
Хмельницкий Вы откуда Я из города Твери
cool Tverskaya
прикольно Тверской
trich How to call a
трич Как правильно назвать
Tver woman correctly
тверичанка
this is about everything Well I
это обо всём Ну
try to talk about the war but most often it
стараюсь о войне общаться но чаще всего
turns out about life for family
получается за жизнь за за семью
hungry
проголодались
again hungry
ещё раз проголодались
damn I
блин я
cooked This is really I don't see you I
приготовил Вот это на самом деле я вас
mean you don't see me So I
не вижу В смысле вы меня не видите Так
communicate with you like
что общаюсь с вами
this I mean you don't
так В смысле не
see I don't see for some reason
видите не вижу почему-то просто
this hexagon just rotates I got it I can
вращается этот шестигранник понял я я
see you for now Yes I do too let me
вас пока вижу Да я тоже давайте я тоже
eat too we will
буду кушать мы вместе будем
eat together well I have too Do you have something
кушать хорошо у меня тоже У вас что там
tasty there Yes I cooked mussels mussels Damn
вкусненького Да я мидии приготовил мидии
well Show this mussel Yeah come on to the
Блин ну Покажите эту мидию Да ну к
camera I can't see it far damn it's a
камере Это я далеко не вижу блин это
laptop Well to the laptop
ноутбук Ну к ноутбуку
and it opens up this
а она раскрывается эта
mussel I've never seen a mussel can you
мидия Я никогда мидию не видел можете
show it in the middle like
показать в середине как
mussels Yeah I don't understand what I'm showing where
мидии Да не понимаю что я куда показываю
here to the laptop camera yes yes Closer even closer and
вотк камере ноутбука да да Ближе ближе
can you turn it in half in front of the camera
а можете её напополам перед камерой
in half so that I've never seen what's inside the
напополам развернуть чтоб что внутри у
mussel
мидии никогда не
Damn cool and you too show me how  eat
Блин прикольно и вы а покажите как едят
midi them somehow there and just swallow like
миди их как-то там а просто глотают вот
that by itself well just for beer I took it I
так сам по себе ну чисто к пиву взял
understood and how are they they in shells these
понял а они как это они в ракушках эти
midi or how Or already without shells usually
миди или как Или уже без ракушек обычно
in shells usually Well I have never eaten like that
в ракушках обычно Ну я так ни разу не ел
I am not an
я не
aristocrat an ordinary factory worker from the
Аристократ обычный заводчанин с
factory bought them these ice cream ice cream
завода купил их эти мороженое мороженое
in the sense that an ordinary person from the
в смысле у вас что простой человек с
factory can afford to
завода может Мити себе позволить
eat Mitya Yes anyone who does not mind the money
кушать Да кто угодно кому денег не жалко
And how much do they cost in
А сколько они стоят
my opinion 350 rubles per pack a
по-моему 350 руб за пачку
pack damn 610
пачка блин 610
g 350
г 350
rubles cool I don't know normal not
руб прикольно Я не знаю нормально не
normal What is this like a snack for
нормально Что такое это как закуска к
beer this is not food this is not food not food finya
пиву это не еда это не еда не еда финя
Yes of course not food and why don't you not
Да конечно не еда а ты что не ей не
get full from these mussels Yes of
наешься этими мидиями Да
course
конечно
Damn what is this how old are you
Капец ну что это сколько те лет
43 43 Voice
43 43 Голос
young not really young hair I
молодой не реально молодой волос я и
look
выгляжу
young I don't see I really speak I
молодо Я не вижу я реально говорю у меня
just have a white screen now and it's good
просто белый экран сейчас и хорошо
Imagine me let me describe myself then a
Представь меня давай я опишу себя значит
person like that in a white shirt Yes uh
человек такой в белой рубашке Да ээ
pretty  appearance with a blue and yellow
симпатичной внешности с сине-жёлтый
flag behind behind the
флагом сзади за
back flag behind the back wait a minute flag behind the
спиной флаг за спиной погоди флаг за
back Yeah,
спиной
come on I'll show you my flag
Да давай те покажу свой флаг
come on Well I hope you understand because I'm
давай Ну надеюсь ты поймёшь потому что я
really just watching Bela right now
сейчас ну реально просто наблюдаю
and I don't understand what I see view what kind of
Белы и не понимаю что я вижу вид что это
flag is this have you played Warcraft brother No
за флаг ты играл в Warcraft брат Нет
you haven't played Warcraft No not a flag can you
Warcraft ты не играл Нет не флаг
see it normally or what Well the flag is ve I don't
нормально видно или как Ну флаг ви Я не
know what it is
знаю а что
Well a computer game from our
тако Ну компьютерная игра из нашего
childhood How old are you 40 43 I have something from my
детства Сколько лет 40 43 у меня что-то
childhood there were second heroes there were also second heroes
детства там герои вторые ещё были вторые
Yeah and who wait for whom did you chop down the
герои Да а кто погоди за кого ты рубил
second heroes I mean by view in short that
вторые герои Я за видом короче то что
titans for sages titans this is order these are where the
титанами за мудрецов титаны это порядок
hell are there druids boars villagers were
блин там друиды кабаны селяне были птица
roc bird wait roc bird these are these are well Orcs
Рух погоди птица Рух это эти это ну Орки
like wait roc birds roc birds they were the
типа погоди птиц Рух птиц Рух у них
first ones these were
первые это
Gremlins no wait not
были Гремлины нет погоди не
Gremlins they have there Dudes on
Гремлины у них там Чуваки на на
wolves not dudes on wolves not where the
волках не чуваки на волках не там где
wolves were  these were the Barbarians there
волки были это эти Варвары были там
Barbarians and the barbarian
Варвары да варва
Kato Klo Orcs who cast
Като кло Орки которые кастую
bloodthirstiness and cast
кровожадность да кастует
And who did you usually play as heroes too
А за кого ты играл обычно в героев тоже
I'm telling you for these in short for the
Я же тебе говорю за вот этих короче за
sages who shoot titans
мудрецов которые титанами стреляют
order yes they have the most powerful
порядок да у них ну самые самые сильные
titans Yes if you got to the titans debt
титаны Да ты если до титанов дол
shooter
стрелком набрался
order they have throats of stone do not throat -
у порядка горли у них камен не горли -
these are already those with
это уже э те что с
dragons Come on heroes the third hero
драконами Да ладно герои третий герой
What heroes look Victor sit down in your place
Какие герои смотри Виктор сядь на место
ses I'll
сес
put Victor Ivanov sit on me no
положу Виктор Иванов сядьте на ме нет у
we have a serious conversation with you
нас к вам серьёзный
now I'll sit down everything I'm sitting down
разговор сейчас я сяду всё Я сажусь
Come on I'm here uh Victor Ivanov
Давай я здесь э Виктор Иванов
look Victor Ivanov
смотрите Виктор Иванов
Yes August 5 on the Internet I'm watching
Да 5 августа в интернете я смотрю 5
August 5, 1988 Yes you know the
августа 1988 года Да ты шаришь нормально
Internet well yes We don't
в интернете да Мы специально не
show our face on purpose in chatroulette This is a
показываем в чатрулетке наше лицо Это
fake production What is
фейковая постанова такая Что
spinning is called substitution of a
крутится это называется подмена
video signal means look uh No I'm not
видеосигнала значит смотрите ээ Да не не
kidding Are you watching every second
прикалываюсь Ты что каждый второй такой
signal like this at  we have an offer for you
сигнал смотрите у нас есть к вам
you What plant do you work at
предложение вы На каком заводе работаете
in Tver And you tell me about me
в Твери А ты скажи ты обо мне
[music] you
[музыка]
know don't want to earn extra money I
знаешь не хотите подзаработать
want I like to earn What
Хочу хочу я люблю зарабатывать Какой у
access do you have at the plant
вас доступ на заводе
I'm a
я
mechanic I understood that mechanics do assembly
слесарь понял что слесари сборочных
work Yes what do you assemble there
работ Да что вы там
excavators military equipment I'm interested
экскаваторы военная техника интересует
no military extremely
нет военная крайне
rare extremely rare usually Civil I
редко крайне редко обычно Гражданская
understood these are these wheeled excavators So so well
понял это эти экскаваторы колёсные Так
based on the Belarusian RA tractor it has a
так ну на базе белоруса ра трактор у
blade in the front and a telescopic working gear in the back
него спереди отвал а сзади рабочка
we
телескопическая это мы
assemble this So are you ready to
собираем Так что вы готовы за деньги
do anything for money for
сделать всё что
example
угодно например
anything let's say we need the coordinates where they
угодно скажем нам нужны Координаты где
repair or make military equipment
ремонтируют или делают военную технику
No well how would I know I don't know well I'll
Нет ну откуда я знаю я ж не знаю ну вас
name you something interesting maybe a name maybe
назву что-то интересное может наз может
some closed workshop where no one is
какой-то цех закрытый куда никого не
allowed No not us eh well
пускают Нет не мы
for the
э ну для
military based on the Ural but the Urals were brought to us
военных на базе Урала но Урал нам
ready that is we ourselves Ura didn't
готовые то есть мы сами Ура не
produce the base Well like a cabin Well and well the
производили базу Ну типа кабина Да и ну
chassis were brought to us ready from the Urals and
шаси нам привозили их готовые из Урала и
we put our own on them Well the
мы ставили на них свои Ну
working dig mechanism  and everyone
рабоч копай механизм и вс
in Ural couldn't do it themselves why did they
в Урале не могли сами сделать это зачем
bring it to you no Ural makes
привозили к Вам нет Урале делают
wheeled equipment Yes but they don't
именно колёсную технику Да но они не
make excavator equipment so it
делают экскаваторную технику поэтому
turns out to be a cooperation Ural makes
получается кооперация Урал делает
wheeled equipment and Tver
колёсную технику а Тверь
makes excavators such a half how many
делает экскаваторы такая полу сколько
excavators does your
экскаваторов делает ваш
x s make
х с
we can't cope we need workers
не справляемся нам работники нужны
damn us and in and out and in the mane you
капец нас и в и в хвост и в гриву
do business How much is
делаете дела Сколько зарплата у
your salary Well well under a hundred some 90 some
вас Ну ну под сотку у кого 90 у кого
70 that's less than a thousand bucks and
70 это меньше штуки баксов и
so we run like crazy
так мы бегаем как сумасшедшие
generally day and night we have vry sm
вообще днм и ночью у намы ври сме
work so-so sometimes it
работаем
works sometimes it doesn't work
чная так себе то работает то не работает
as it wants night shift
как хочет ночная смена
sa goes fingers bend like we
са ходит пальцы гнут типа мы
earn Well because night shift is a part-time
зарабатываем Ну потому что ночная смена
job well you understand yourself at night they
подработка ну ты сам понимаешь в ночь
pay extra that's
доплачивают
enough to
вот да хватит
eat Yes I drain the excess water
жрать Да я воду сливаю лишнюю
[applause] there
[аплодисменты]
were saboteurs at our plant so they would
заводе были Диверсанты так что бы они
most likely have done the most
скорее всего сделали самое
effectively
эффективно
Well I would have handed them over first of all no no so
Ну я бы их сдал бы в первую очередь нене
that if these  The saboteurs wanted to
чтоб если бы эти Диверсанты захотели
do something nasty so that they would
сделать что-то пакостно так чтобы они
do drugs, distribute them, not
сделали наркотики распространяли бы не
exactly like that, so that the plant would stop the
именно такое чтобы завод остановить там
production process there and break it, but no way, I
процесс производственны и поломать как а
think, I think, no way, I think,
никак я думаю я думаю никак думаю
because we pass through the checkpoint and we have
потому что мы проходим проходную и у нас
two guards standing there and they have these Well,
там по два охранника стоит и у них эти
metal files like these
Ну металлические пилки такие
Kote, we can't even bring beer to work
Коте мы Даже пиво не можем на работу
You have a birthday, I understand, you
принести у тебя День Рождения понял ты
want a birthday with the guys,
хочешь день рождения с мужиками
okay, yeah And if, for example,
хорошо да А если если например
saboteurs who, for example, would
Диверсанты которые например дроном
simply hit the plant with a drone Where? They would
просто ударят по заводу Куда Вот они бы
hit it so that the plant,
ударили так чтобы завод
some kind of
электроподстанция какой-то
super-hand electrical substation, to a friend, in one workshop, another workshop, the
суперхенд другу в один цех другой цех
target What is the most key node in
намер Какой самый такой ключевой узел в
this plant, that without it everything will become
этом заводе что без него всё
I think
станет Я думаю
under the station, yes, that is, it is necessary under the station
под станцию да то есть надо под станцию
If you will, if a person was
Если будешь если человек был
saboteurs at the door Look at the map, I
диверсантов в двери Посмотри по карте
understand I don't know
понял Не знаю
Okay, okay, do you have any questions for me Well,
Ладно хорошо есть у тебя ко мне вопросы
I understand that you are trolling me, you're not
Ну я понял что ты меня троллишь не
just kidding,
просто прикалываешься
I'm quite serious You're just
я вполне серьёзный Ты просто
kidding,
прикалываешься
no, you're not kidding, so you're not kidding, my
нет как ты не прикалываешься так не
work is at  me like that I
прикалываюсь работа у меня такая я
find good people and we are
нахожу людей хороших и мы
hard it's huge Well look how
тяжело он же огромный Ну смотри вот как
ours beat oil refineries
наши бьют нефтеперерабатывающие заводы
Yes there is a primary oil processing unit Yes
Да есть установка первичной обработки
aftsh they hit it with a drone and that's it and the
нефти Да афтш лупят её дроном и всё и
whole plant stops because without it
весь завод встаёт потому что без неё
nothing goes on so they hit at
ничего дальше не идёт так бьют то на
random I mean they hit at ugat at ugat But in
угад В смысле на уга на угат бьют Но в
every plant they get into this aftsh
каждом заводе попадают в эту афтш
yeah Well Wait Wait Wait Wait Wait Wait Wait I'm
да Ну Погоди Стой стой Погоди Стой
buzzing Now wait I'll come I'll get a
Погоди Стой жужу Сейчас погоди я приду Я
beer now Wait Wait do
сейчас пиво возьму Погоди
n't disconnect people throw in donations for now trim
Стой не отключайся народ закиньте пока
we are without svitla sadomo
донаты тримайте мы без свитла садомо
throw in trim the
закиньте тримайте
channel here is not left I'm back Yes
канале здесь нет ушёл я вернулся
yes the plant it's oh so big in
Дада завод он же о же большой по
territory so how can you hit
территории так как как можно ударить
a [ __ ]
[__]
point by coordinate occupies a huge
точечно по координата занимает огромную
Well the drone flies to him coordinates in bili it
Ну Дрон летит ему координаты в били он
lands on coordinates exactly that
приземляется на координаты именно то
is you want to say that in Ukraine
есть ты хочешь сказать что на Украине
there are some
есть какие-то
people who are giving up the positions of their plant or
люди которые сдают позиции своего завода
what not in Ukraine but in Russia there are
что ли не на Украине а в России есть
people  here I find people who want to make
люди вот я нахожу людей которые хотят
money they know for example in their
заработать они знают например в своём
plant because Well the one who launches
заводе потому что Ну тот кто запускает у
these various airplanes here doesn't know the
нас эти всякие самолётики он не знает
plant and the one who works there knows where the
завод а тот кто работает он знает где на
key
заводе ключевые
components are in the plant and they directly tell you listen look
узлы что и прямо сообщают слушай смотри
I'll need to run now Write me
мне нужно будет сейчас бежать Напиши мне
your phone number here in the chat I'll
тут в чатике свой номер телефона я
write you in detail tomorrow
короче завтра напишу тебе детально
options I would without questions I'm
варианты Я бы без вопросов Я тебе
telling you seriously I'm telling you without saying my
серьёзно говорю я я без говорю у меня
whole screen is white just no well besides
весь экран белый просто нет ну помимо
white no Look don't Switch take
бело нет Смотри не Переключай возьми
write in the chat write me your
напиши в чатике напиши мне свой номер
phone number I'll save tomorrow I'll write to you I'm
телефона я сохраню завтра напишу тебе я
telling you that right now I don't have a chat
тебе говорю что сечас чата нету у меня
here Zen bookmark Bookmark chat roulette
вот Zen закладка Закладка чат-рулетка
where I chose chat roulette and the third
где я выбрал чат-рулетку и третья
bookmark is a free vcam chat dash
закладка - это бесплатный vcam чат тире
and then I don't see and that's it and just Pony
и дальше я не вижу и всё и просто Поня
line TPS double double with Pony Then
строчка TPS двойная двойная с Поня Тогда
then tell me I'll
тогда скажи мне я
write down yes
запишу да
700 Yes yes
700 Дада
900 900
900 900
people donate and throw in  have a
народ донать и закиньте майте
conscience Hello Where are you from Russia
совесть Здравствуйте Вы откуда России
Siberia What do you communicate with Yes,
сибир чем общаетесь
just like that, depending on my mood What
Да так просто вот по настроению что О
will have to I understood how you feel about the fact that
чём придётся понял как относишься к тому
Russia attacked
что Россия напала на
Ukraine Well, yes, I feel normal and what is
Украину Ну да нормально отношусь а чем
normal Well, because of what it
нормально Ну там же из-за чего это
started because of the fact that you began to
началось из-за того то что вы начали
oppress the Russian
притеснять русский
language I understood how many cases are there in the Russian
язык понял сколько падежей в русском
language
языке
now and What are you laughing at how many how many well
сейчас а Что смеёшься сколько сколько ну
you're like asking by analogy with you have some kind of
ты типа задаёшь по аналогу с у тебя
list Are there any questions you
список какой-то Есть какие-то вопрос
give I studied Russian in Ukraine
даёшь я вот русский язык учил в Украине
you studied in Russia how many cases are there in the
ты учил в России сколько падежей в
Russian language Well, I'm telling you now I'll tell you Are you
русском языке Ну я тебе говорю сейчас
waiting for someone to
скажу Ты ждёшь что чтоб тебе это
tell you this raise your hands no this is not Google
подсказали руки подними не это не Гугли
Come on and look at me and not in the chat
Давай и смотри на меня а не в чат
How many pages how many cases are there in the Russian
Сколько паже сколько падежей в русском
language Let's
языке Давай
count six
считаю шесть
no And what is on nazovi and
нет А какой на назови и
nominative a seven
именительный а семь
nominative nominative genitive dative
именительный именительный родительный
accusative e
дательный винительный э
So
Так
wait Why sem if she Nazovi Nazovi se se
подожди Почему сем если ше Назови Назови
nu nominative genitive
се се ну именительный родительный
dative
дательный
accusative instrumental  proposed and
винительный творительный предложенный и
But the seventh I don't really know for
А вот седьмой Я не знаю реально
half an hour you can't remember sko
полчаса не можешь вспомнить ско
pozha I'm explaining to you What's the joke of your
пожа Я же те Объясняю В чём прикол твоих
questions the joke is that you
вопросов прикол в том что ты свой
don't know your Russian language and you're telling them to
русский язык не знаешь и рассказываешь
oppress you here Come on are you going or not
тут притеснять Давай идёшь или не ид
id Okay let's talk normally What am
Ладно давай поговорим нормально На каком
I speaking now speak Russian correctly
я сейчас разговори на русском верно
How many letters are in the Russian alphabet Yes I wo
Сколько букв в русском алфавите Да я те
n't name them How many
не буду называть Сколько букв в русском
letters are in the Russian alphabet How many
алфавите Сколько букв в русском Смотри
letters are in Russian Look this is first grade even in kindergarten sko letters
это первый класс даже в садике ско букв
in the Russian alphabet is that how they teach it in kindergarten I'm
в русском алфавите это в садике учат так
first grade or something How many letters are in the
я первый класс что ли Сколько букв в
Russian
русском
alphabet 33 I think 32 like teeth
алфавите 33 вроде вроде 32 как зубов
Yes in kindergarten They also say 32 like teeth it's
Да в садике Ещё говорят 32 как зубов
very easy to remember
запомнить очень просто
[music]
[музыка]
m You just damn me how do you count
м Ты просто блин я ты как считаешь
wait how do you count
подожди ты как
a BB And so on well name it how do you
считаешь а ББ И так дальше ну назови как
count 32 letters What do you call it why should I call you the
считай 32 буквы Ты что назови зачем я
whole alphabet Well you
тебе буду называть весь алфавит А ну
see Well you see I'm te go 33
видишь Ну видишь я те го 33
32 which letter didn't you count Name the
32 какую ты букву не посчитал Назови
last three letters
последние три буквы
run three  letters yayu e Oh e it I
бегом три буквы яю е Ой
it I right and right eyu ya Well
е ею я ею я правильно а правильно эю я
okay let it be so damn in
Ну ладно пусть ты будет так блин в
Ukraine Russian language or in you in Russia
Украине русский язык или у вас в России
oppress people In short it seems to me it is necessary to
притеснять лю Короче мне кажется надо
start not Wait Look you stupidly do not
начать не Подожди Смотри ты тупо не
know elementary things of your language
знаешь элементарных вещей своего языка
Yes you do not know elementary just
Да ты не знаешь элементарных просто
elementary Yes no it is not at all it is not in
элементарных Да нет это вообще это не по
essence you even say those well look You
сути ты даже говоришь те ну посмотри Ты
can't listen look you have
не можешь выслушать смотри у тебя есть
some specific questions that you
конкретно какие-то вопросы которые ты
ask each person right not
задаёшь каждому человеку верно не
everyone you told me just because
каждому ты мне сказал просто с изза того
here oppress Russian languages I decided to
что тут притес русские языки я решил
see how you know it Russian not
посмотреть как ты знаешь это руский не у
you have the flag of Ukraine hanging in the background you have
тебя висит на фоне флаг Украины у тебя
this what is it called trident of Ukraine
этот как он называется трезубец
what did I call Ukraine America Yes you
украи я что назвал Украины Америки Да ты
generally just yes no no yes what do
вообще просто да нет нет
you also get your flag to
да что тебе достать тоже свой флаг
hang on get come on well hang Well why fly Well I do
повесить на доста давай ну повешать Ну а
n't know fly if that's how
зачем повей Ну не знаю пове если так у
you have everything here I am now communicating look
тебя все вот я сейчас общающихся смотри
you threw it like a rag just T threw it
ты его кинул как тряпку просто Т кинул
on the bed and that's it
на кровать и
You  you are embarrassed by your flag you are
всё Ты стесняешься своего флага
embarrassed by the
стесняешься
Russian language you don't know the flag you have
русский язык не знаешь флаг у тебя
lying around in short simplicity you are telling me now
короче валяется простоты ты мне сейчас
what you want to hear that's
говоришь то что ты хочешь слышать вот и
all I am telling you you have
всё Я же тебе говорю у тебя под каждого
every question for each person you just express
человека каждый вопрос Ты просто Выра
No I have a question for you Look you
Нет у меня под тебя вопрос Вот смотри ты
said that you said that in Ukraine
сказал что ты сказал что в Украине
oppressed
утесняемый
and I know the answers But you don't
и я знаю ответы А ты не
know well List the Russian alphabet
знаешь ну Перечисли русский алфавит
Come on why should I list it for you Well
Давай зачем я тебе буду перечислять Ну
you are proving that there Why should I
ты же доказываешь то что там Зачем мне
list it I went In short how are you like to
перечислять я шёл Короче как ты типа
answer questions there and then you
чтобы там отвечать на вопросы а ты тогда
sit in chat roulette in order to, in short,
сидишь в чат рулетке чтобы короче
breed people like
разводить таких как
you breed And how did you breed me well here you
ты разводить А как ты меня развёл ну вот
bred into cases bred into letters bred into what
развёл на падежи развёл короче на буквы
you bred And how many
развёл на то что ты развёл А сколько
cases are there in the Ukrainian language
падежей в украинском языке
seven Guessed
сем Угадал
Guessed Well why are you proving that in
Угадал Ну почему ты доказываешь то что в
Russian okay listen in short don't cry
русском ладно слушай короче не плачь
just don't cry Yes Who is crying who is crying you are you are
просто не плачь Да Кто плачет кто плачет
really I am look Do you know  said that they
реально я жа смотри Знаешь ты сказал что
started their own because in short here in
сво начали потому что короче тут в
Ukraine
Украине
about 32 letters he already doubted that
про 32 буквы он уже засомневался что
maybe the 3rd one is at the beginning of your alphabet
может 3 я е е у вас в начале алфавита
Here it is Hello Hello
Вот
where are you from this is k and
откуда это к
who is this right no blue And show me
а это кто правый нет синий А покажи у
you don't have the right sector you have white at the
тебя не правый сектор у тебя белый ещё
top isn't this Right
вверху не это Правый
sector Right sector is Nor Why is there a
сектор Правый сектор это Нор Почему
blue stripe and not a black one this is black it
синяя полоска а не чёрная это чёрная
just shines like that
просто так отсвечивает
Right sector - Who are they
Правый сектор - Это кто они
normal raise up ka Look this is
нормальные повыше подыми кам Смотри это
black I'm going to
чёрный я те сейчас
turn on some Donetsk now Donetsk Handsome
включу какой-то Донецк Донецк Красава то
you say Right sector Shah Donetsk When is it possible to be on first name terms with you yes
Ты когда Ну можно можно с тобой на ты да
yes it is possible When I saw the yellow stripe at the
да можно Я когда увидел жёлтую полоску
bottom you it I think you are burning Right
внизу ты её Я думаю ты горишь Правый
sector what yellow is this Donetsk Where are you from
сектор какой жёлтый это Донец Ты откуда
bro we are from Russia from Yekaterinburg Yekaterinburg I
братан ж мы мы с России с екатеренбурга
understood what you are talking about
Екб понял о чём общаетесь
and now with two girls from Donetsk they
да сейчас с двумя девчонками с Донецка
were talking normal there and the phone died We are
говорили нормальные там и телефон сел Мы
generally so normal with them Urali understood  I
вообще так нормально с ними урали понял
understood
понял
from Donetsk but now I live in
из Донец но сейчас живу в
Makeyevka And before that there were three Ukrainians,
Макеевке А до этого три украинца были
well, adults there probably, well, for
это ну взрослые там наверно ну за
fifty there, like that, like that,
полтинник там вот так вот
for historians, in short. In short, I did
это под историков короче Короче так я и
nt understand the aggression, it disappeared in the roulette,
не понял агрессия под пропала в рулетке
right away, its useless. And now,
вот сразу же сходу бесполезно А сейчас
in short, they are
короче они
for Ukraine and
за Укра и
Ukrainian. Well done, and then I say. Well, Im
украински Молодец а я потом говорю Ну я
from Donetsk, like, I live in Makeyevka.
вот с Донецка да типа живу в Макеевке
Why did you bomb us for 8 years and theyre
Почему вы нас бомбили 8 лет и они
starting to say something,
начинают уже что-то там
what are they saying to us Russians? Why did you attack
чему нам россиянам говорят Почему вы На
us,
нас напали
protect us, now they seem to have
защищайте нас сечас вот вром вроде
started to protect us. And now everyone has forgotten. In short, theyre
начали защищать А теперь все забили
shelling us, and theyre still defending us.
Короче нас обстреливают сейчас до сих
How do you understand that theyre not defending? I mean, we had it
Украина Как понять не защищают В смысле
further, had it passed? Well,
у нас же это дальше же прошли Ну так
where did they pass in the Zaporizhzhya Kherson
куда прошли в Запорожской Херсонской
region? We had it near
области приш У нас под
Donetsk, [ __ ], 5 km Avdiivka, from
Донецком было Вот адос 5 км Авдеевка от
which Avdiivka was
этого авдеевку
liberated,
освободили
15, and theyre going somewhere. This is on TV.
15 дальше идут где-то это вам по телику
They were taken to Kursk, we had this
Их забрали на Курск у нас стояла вот эта
Brigade, even our Donetsk one.  Like that's what it's
Бригада даже наша Донецкая Типа так
called now now now for Sorry, I'll
называется сечас сейчас сейчас за Извини
interrupt now for Toretsk they're fighting so
перебью сейчас за торецк бьются так
look at you Donetsk is still being
смотри тебе ещё Донецк до сих пор
shelled They still have
обстреливают у нас от Донецка до сих пор
n't withdrawn Ukrainian troops from Donetsk we had
не отвели украинские войска у нас были
No well, excuse me What's your name Andrey
Нет ну ты извини Как тебя зовут Андрей
Andrey well, excuse me well guys yes they're dying
Андрей ну ты извини ну парни да погибают
There's like they're storming I can't
Там как бы это штурмуют по Я не могу
understand why you can't free us for so many years
понять почему Вы за столько лет не
How
освободить Как
why Because they don't want
почему Потому что не хотят
peace because of this look if if
мирк из-за этого смотри если бы если бы
in fact they are needed piecemeal and
по сути их же получается штучно надо а
if they were to level everything with planes no well
если бы самолётами заровнять всё не ну
Bach Bakhmut is normal Zarov and all the VH
Бах бахмут нормально Заров и всё ВХ
population was occupied liberated
населения было заняли освободили
all the cities or something like that they'll
все города что ли те таким
kill the whole world and then Well
как тогда убьют весь мирк а потом Ну
let them come out they'd give them apartments in
пусть выйдут дали б квартиры в
Krasnodar somewhere merku and that's it would leave
Краснодаре где-то мерку и всё выехал бы
and And how are you cooking you now while they're
и А как ты вые сейчас тебя варят пока
leaving Well, like they're damn Let them
выезжать будут Ну типа они блин Пусть
leave in Kyiv through Belarus in short
выедут в Киеве через Беларусь короче
Let them come back somehow I don't know There you
Пусть возвращаются как-то Я не знаю Там
see you yourself understand a lot of
же видишь ты сам понимаешь много
civilians who like  well, should we
населения мирных которые как бы ну это
bomb everyone or something like that So in essence if
всех бомбить что ли Так бы по сути если
we would well Our country acted like the
бы мы бы ну Наша страна действовала как
Great Patriotic War and there is no point, you
Великую Отечественную и нет смысла же
understand, or how Or like the Americans this is
понимаешь или как Или как американцы это
Yugoslavia that is the point Now take Ukraine to
югославию вот смысл Сейчас Украину взять
go to Lvov and Well that is right well
пройти до Львова и Ну так правильно ну
look I will say So we we in Donetsk and
так смотри я скажу Так мы мы в Донецке и
Makeyevka in the second year we
в Макеевке в 2 втором году мы с лагами
went out with lags met Russia because well it
выходили Россию встречали потому что ну
was a holiday we thought everything now a
это было праздник мы думали всё сейчас
week or two and everything will be over they will take Kyiv
неделя две и всё закончится возьмут Киев
and now really 3 years in Donetsk
а теперь реально 3 года у нас в Донецке
in general all the factories are now closed because there is
вообще заводы все теперь закрыты потому
shelling just the mines
что идут обстрелы просто Шахты
have closed the youth are all leaving Well
позакрывали молодёжь вся уезжает Да ну
what are the old people left there a little In short
что остаются старики там немножко Короче
guys that's when it all started Well I
пацаны вот когда вся началась Вот я
definitely didn't think that it would be in a week I immediately
точно не думал что это за неделю я сразу
thought it would be at least for 10 years and I think
думал это минимум на 10 лет и я думаю
it will be like that That is to say you want to
это так и будет То есть ты хочешь
say that you will chill there in Yekaterinburg for
сказать что вы там в Екатеринбурге
10 years and we in Makeyevka and
будете 10 лет чилить а мы т в Макеевке и
Donetsk will suffer for 10 years Why
Донецке будем 10 лет страдать Почему мы
will we  chill out the war will not be with
будем чилить война же будет не с
Ukraine Ukraine - It's just yeah well
Украиной Украина - Это же просто да ну
like you look we have shelling in Donetsk and
типа у тебя смотри у нас в Донецке и в
Makeyevka you have shelling in Yekaterinburg
Макеевке обстрел у тебя в Екатеринбурге
no you're at least 10 years old at least 20 Why I'm
нет тебе хоть 10 лет Хоть 20 Почему Я же
explaining to you right now Ukraine is a
тебе объясняю вот сейчас Украина - это
warm-up and then there will be a general
разминка а потом будет всё общая
mobilization and war with Europe I
мобилизация и война с Европой я вот так
think everyone will go to arms there I understand And have you
думаю там все по ружьё пойдут понял А ты
already been to the
уже ходил в
military registration and enlistment office No I didn't go to the army no
военкомат Нет я не ходил в армии не
That is you don't give a damn about Donetsk
То есть ты тебе на Донецк наплевать
Why don't I give a damn those I
Почему мне наплевать те Я
serve And where is something I don't see that g in the
служу А где что-то я не вижу что г в
Slavic Brigade And what And what do you want
Славянской бригаде А что А что ты хочешь
so that I'm from what I've been in
чтобы вот я с чего я с четырнадцатого
Kramatorsk Slavyansk since the fourteenth year and
года и в Краматорск Славянск были да
then they retreated to Donetsk Yes we have like
потом отошли на Донецк Да у нас типа
we're working at home for a month No well there will
идёт мы э работаем месяц дома Не ну
be a draft Of course we'll go Well guys yes they
будет призыв Конечно пойдём Ну парни да
fight if the question is hundred Wait stop stop stop
воюют если вопрос ста Подожди Стоп стоп
then you really are you two Yes you are
стоп то вы реально вот вы двое Да вы
some Maybe you went to the training ground there
какой-то Может на полигон ходили там
learned something or what kind of training ground I'm
учились что-то или что какой полигон Я
in the defense industry I'm [ __ ] you I'm making you air defense
на оборонке Я вам [__] я вам делаю ПВО
pro What air defense pro [ __ ] we are being bombed
проро Какое ПВО проро блин нас бомбят
shelled you have this not on your oil
обстреливают у вас на это на не на нефте
plants [ __ ] in short they fly from these
заводы ваши Блин короче долетают от по
drones what kind of anti-missile damn air defense what
эти дроны какое противоракетной блин ПВО
No This is our
какое Нет Это у нас тут
Right Sector not And this is Donetsk Yes Donetsk
Правый сектор не А это Донецк Да Донецк
now from Donetsk like pi
сейчас оты Донецк лайк пи
comment write to y Telegram right now axis
комент пись на й Telegram прям зараз ось
VN
ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube is busy with
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through scarg Orcs in your ban and very
нас через скарг Орки в твый бан и дуже
many videos I don't show people at times I don't
багато видео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that we Mali operational links are
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
written right now and while there in Telegram OKM videos
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
there is also interesting and useful
окм вдео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are sorry for you
информация и ми повинни з вами тримати
constant operational links
постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that chi will show you
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube process Slava ukraini letter
YouTube Слава украини пись